<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Hello Haileys</title>
    <link>https://hellohaileys.github.io/</link>
    <description>Recent content on Hello Haileys</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 09 Apr 2018 12:00:00 -0700</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://hellohaileys.github.io/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>California Dreaming 2018</title>
      <link>https://hellohaileys.github.io/blog/2018/04/09-california_dreaming/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 09 Apr 2018 12:00:00 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hellohaileys.github.io/blog/2018/04/09-california_dreaming/</guid>
      <description>If California is for dreamers, catch me sleeping.

(Continuing on from our last story, where we stopped in Jacksonville, which you can read about here&amp;hellip;)
Ever since I arrived to Portland in January, it&amp;rsquo;s been cloudy and rainy. So you can imagine how thrilled I was to go to California, where the sunshine and vitamin D is abundant.

When visiting a place, I like to see how the locals see it, as well as the tourist areas.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Road Trip Through Oregon</title>
      <link>https://hellohaileys.github.io/blog/2018/04/04-road_trip_through_oregon/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 04 Apr 2018 12:00:00 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hellohaileys.github.io/blog/2018/04/04-road_trip_through_oregon/</guid>
      <description>Last Month, Jordan and I were able to set out on our first road trip from Oregon down to California. We didn&amp;rsquo;t realize how fun the stop along the way would be.
Driving down from Oregon to California is a 13+ hour drive. Basically the distance from Johannesburg to Cape Town in South Africa. That&amp;rsquo;s when I really realised how big America is.
The first stop we made was in Jacksonville, Oregon.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>8 Reasons To Start a Blog</title>
      <link>https://hellohaileys.github.io/blog/2018/03/10-why_we_began_blogging/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 10 Mar 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hellohaileys.github.io/blog/2018/03/10-why_we_began_blogging/</guid>
      <description>Hey there! So&amp;hellip;our blog is finally up! I&amp;rsquo;d been toying with the idea for years, and finally last September, while Jordan and I were still in a long distance relationship I sent him a text, finally admitting to myself that I wanted to start a blog one day.
Six months later, the idea has finally come together. I always wanted to blog about curly hair. I&amp;rsquo;m passionate about natural hair and felt all my trial and error experiences could be passed on to other curly girls.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>D&#39;s Hair Routine</title>
      <link>https://hellohaileys.github.io/blog/2018/03/08-hair_routine/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 08 Mar 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hellohaileys.github.io/blog/2018/03/08-hair_routine/</guid>
      <description>Most naturalistas are hair junkies. Not necessarily because we&amp;rsquo;re hoarders, but because we&amp;rsquo;re constantly on the lookout for the next &amp;ldquo;best&amp;rdquo; hair product. Something that&amp;rsquo;s gonna save us time and give our hair that perfect bounce&amp;hellip;
I don&amp;rsquo;t know if it&amp;rsquo;s possible to reach that point of being perfectly happy with our hair. Personally, even on good hair days I could walk into a shop, see a new product, and think &amp;ldquo;maybe this is going to revolutionise the way I do my hair&amp;rdquo;.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>He&#39;s Gotta Love Your Natural Hair</title>
      <link>https://hellohaileys.github.io/blog/2018/03/05-hes_gotta_love_your_natural_hair/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 05 Mar 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hellohaileys.github.io/blog/2018/03/05-hes_gotta_love_your_natural_hair/</guid>
      <description>I remember the night I met Jordan. I had just cut my hair pretty short and was attempting to rock corn rows on the side with the rest of my curls. The hair cut didn&amp;rsquo;t quite go as planned and I didn&amp;rsquo;t feel like I was looking my prettiest.
The sweet thing is, when it&amp;rsquo;s his turn to retell the story about how we met, it goes something along the lines of &amp;ldquo;I saw this cute curly girl who I thought I&amp;rsquo;d probably never see again&amp;hellip;&amp;rdquo;.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>